Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files F-J, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files J
    - Jones, Rosalind D. (Box A-67, Folder 231)
      Photographer if identified: Herbert Hawkins, James L. League
    - Jones, Roy (Box A-67, Folder 232)
    - Jones, Ruby (Box A-67, Folder 233)
    - Jones, Rudolph W. (Box A-67, Folder 234)
    - Jones, Rupert Doc (Box A-67, Folder 235)
    - Jones, Ruppert (Box A-67, Folder 236)
    - Jones, Russell M. (Box A-67, Folder 237)
    - Jones, Ruth (Box A-67, Folder 238)
      Also one photocopied image.
    - Jones, Sam (Box A-67, Folder 239)
    - Jones, Samuel J. (Box A-67, Folder 240)
    - Jones, Samuel L. (Box A-67, Folder 241)
    - Jones, Sarah (Box A-67, Folder 242)
      Photographer if identified: Lillian Wright
    - Jones, Scott C. (Lt.) (Box A-67, Folder 243)
    - Jones, Sharise & Sherrie (Box A-67, Folder 244)
      Photographer if identified: Michael Stanley
    - Jones, Shaun Baker- (Box A-67, Folder 245)
    - Jones, Sheila H. (Box A-67, Folder 246)
    - Jones, Sonia (Box A-67, Folder 247)
    - Jones, Tamiko (Box A-67, Folder 248)
    - Jones, Ted (Box A-67, Folder 249)
    - Jones, Thomas Russell (Box A-67, Folder 250)
    - Jones, Thad (Box A-67, Folder 251)
    - Jones, Thelma (Box A-67, Folder 252)
    - Jones, Theodore (Box A-67, Folder 253)
    - Jones, Theodore (Box A-67, Folder 254)
      Photographer if identified: Jeanne Hedge
    - Jones, Theodore A. (Box A-67, Folder 255)
    - Jones, Theodore J. (Rev.) (Box A-67, Folder 256)
      Photographer if identified: Nesfield Photo
    - Jones, Theodore M. (Box A-67, Folder 257)
    - Jones, Theresa (Box A-67, Folder 258)
    - Jones, Theron (Box A-67, Folder 259)
    - Jones, Thom (Box A-67, Folder 260)
    - Jones, Thomas C. (Rev.) (Box A-67, Folder 261)
      Photographer if identified: C. Jones
    - Jones, Thomas D. (Box A-67, Folder 262)
    - Jones, Thomas Wade (Box A-67, Folder 263)
    - Jones, Timothy (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-67, Folder 264)
    - Jones, Tom (Box A-67, Folder 265)
    - Jones, Van (Mrs.) (Box A-67, Folder 266)
    - Jones, Venzella (Box A-67, Folder 267)
    - Jones, Vernon (Box A-67, Folder 268)
    - Jones, Veronica (Box A-67, Folder 269)
    - Jones, Vicki (Box A-67, Folder 270)
    - Jones, Vinetti (Box A-67, Folder 271)
      Photographer if identified: Emma Rivera
    - Jones, Viola (Box A-67, Folder 272)
    - Jones, Viran K. (Box A-67, Folder 273)
    - Jones, Virginia (Box A-67, Folder 274)
    - Jones, W (Box A-67, Folder 275)
    - Jones, Walter (Box A-67, Folder 276)
    - Jones, Walter (Box A-67, Folder 277)
      One print is a Polaroid. Also a 2-leaf photocopied press release.
    - Jones, J. Walter (Box A-67, Folder 278)
      Photographer if identified: Smith, Dummett
    - Jones, Walter G. (Box A-67, Folder 279)
    - Jones, Walter (Mrs.) (Box A-67, Folder 280)
      Photographer if identified: M. G. Kelsey
    - Jones, Walter Jr. (Box A-67, Folder 281)
    - Jones, Walter (Walt) Jr. (Box A-67, Folder 282)
    - Jones, Warren (Box A-67, Folder 283)
    - Johnson, Sterling (Box A-67, Folder 284)
      Also a 2-leaf press release and one velox print.
    - Jones, W. Yerby (Dr.) (Box A-68, Folder 1)
    - Jones, Waverly M. (Box A-68, Folder 2)
    - Jones, G. Williams (Dr.) (Box A-68, Folder 3)
    - Jones, W.A. (Box A-68, Folder 4)
    - Jones, Willene A. (Box A-68, Folder 5)
      Photographer if identified: Ruffus Merritt
    - Jones, Thomas R. Judge (Box A-68, Folder 6)
      Photographer if identified: King Photographers, Mickey Pallas, Rufus Merritt
    - Jones, Thomas W. (Dr.) (Box A-68, Folder 7)
    - Jones, Tom (Box A-68, Folder 8)
    - Jones, Veronica (Box A-68, Folder 9)
      Photographer if identified: Jerri A. Bass
    - Jones, Vivian M. (Box A-68, Folder 10)
    - Jones, Wendy D. (Box A-68, Folder 11)
    - Jones, J. Wesley (Box A-68, Folder 12)
    - Jones, Wilbur (Rev.) (Box A-68, Folder 13)
      Photographer if identified: C & C Photo Studio
    - Jones, Wm. (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-68, Folder 14)
    - Jones, William B. (Box A-68, Folder 15)
    - Jones, William C. (Box A-68, Folder 16)
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, News Voice International,
    - Jones, William F. (Box A-68, Folder 17)
    - Jones, William H. (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-68, Folder 18)
      Photographer if identified: Harold T. Cooper
    - Jones, William H. (Box A-68, Folder 19)
    - Jones, William M. (Rev.) (Box A-68, Folder 20)
    - Jones, Wm. O. (Box A-68, Folder 21)
    - Jones, Willie (Box A-68, Folder 22)
      Photographer if identified: John Barrett
    - Jones, Willie (Rev.) (Box A-68, Folder 23)
    - Jones, William A., Jr. (Rev.) (Box A-68, Folder 24)
      Two prints have paste residue on verso. One print is cut out and mounted on paper.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Monclova, Dave Greene, Ace Creative Photos
    - Jones, William A., Jr. (Rev.) (Box A-68, Folder 25)
      Also four velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Charles Reiche, Harris Photo, Monclova, Dave Greene, Ace Creative Photos, Vernon L. Smith, Alex Hamilton, Crest Photographers, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Jones, Yasmin (Box A-68, Folder 26)
    - Jones, Yvonne (Box A-68, Folder 27)
      Photographer if identified: Keystone Pictures Inc, James C. Campbell, Keno-Foto
    - Jones-Bey, Hassaun Ali (Box A-68, Folder 28)
    - Joneses, The (Group) (Box A-68, Folder 29)
    - Jonson, Lad (Box A-68, Folder 30)
    - Jonsson, Judyann (Box A-68, Folder 31)
    - Joplin, Scott (Box A-68, Folder 32)
    - Jordan, Aludustus (Dr.) (Box A-68, Folder 33)
      Photographer if identified: Suellen Snyder
    - Jordan, Andrea (Box A-68, Folder 34)
    - Jones, Barbara (Box A-68, Folder 35)
      Also three velox prints, one of which is adhered to paper. One print has lengthy ms. caption on verso.
      Photographer if identified: Newell Johnson, Leon M. Gurley, The Black Marketing Group,
    - Jordan, Carl R. (Mrs.) (Box A-68, Folder 36)
      Print is adhered to a piece of cardstock.
    - Jordan, Clifford (Box A-68, Folder 37)
    - Jordan, Cross (Box A-68, Folder 38)
    - Jordan, Daryl E. (Box A-68, Folder 39)
    - Jordon, David (Box A-68, Folder 40)
    - Jordan, Donna (Box A-68, Folder 41)
    - Jordan, Edgar (Box A-68, Folder 42)
      Print is attached to folder with paste.
    - Jordan, Edwin (Box A-68, Folder 43)
    - Jordan, Eva (Mrs.) (Box A-68, Folder 44)
    - Jordan, Fania (Box A-68, Folder 45)
    - Jordan, Fred (Box A-68, Folder 46)
    - Jordan, Frederick D. (Rev.) (Box A-68, Folder 47)
      Photographer if identified: D.B. Willis
    - Jordan, Gloria (Box A-68, Folder 48)
      Photographer if identified: Colls. H. Davis Jr.
    - Jordan, Grace Hale (Mrs.) (Box A-68, Folder 49)
      Print has single-leaf press release attached on verso.
    - Jordan, Harold B. (Box A-68, Folder 50)
    - Jordan, Honorec (Box A-68, Folder 51)
    - Jordan, Howard Jr. (Dr.) (Box A-68, Folder 52)
    - Jordan, Ike (Box A-68, Folder 53)
    - Jordan, Irene (Box A-68, Folder 54)
      Both prints have single typescript press release leaves attached.
    - Jordan, Ishbel (Box A-68, Folder 55)
    - Jordan, Jack (Box A-68, Folder 56)
      Photographer if identified: Leslie DiRusso, Ebet Roberts
    - Jordan, James A. (Box A-68, Folder 57)
    - Jordan, James E. (Box A-68, Folder 58)
    - Jordan, Joe (Box A-68, Folder 59)
    - Jordan, Joe (Box A-68, Folder 60)
      One print has caption adhered to recto with staples on border.
    - Jordan, June (Box A-68, Folder 61)
    - Jordan, Larry (Box A-68, Folder 62)
    - Jordan, Leon (Box A-68, Folder 63)
    - Jordan, Lois (Box A-68, Folder 64)
    - Jordan, Louis (Box A-68, Folder 65)
      Also one paper stereotype matrix with single-leaf press release attached with paperclip.
    - Jordan, Louis (Box A-68, Folder 66)
      Note on folder: "and his Tympany Five." Also one paper stereotype matrix.
    - Jordan, Louis (Mrs.) (Box A-68, Folder 67)
    - Jordan, Leona (Box A-68, Folder 68)
    - Jordan, Margo (Box A-68, Folder 69)
      One print has typescript leaf resume attached on verso; one is cut out.
    - Jordan, McDonald (Box A-68, Folder 70)
    - Jordan, Margaret J. (Box A-68, Folder 71)
    - Jordan, Nathaniel J. (Box A-68, Folder 72)
    - Jordan, Norma (Box A-68, Folder 73)
    - Jordan, Norma (Box A-68, Folder 74)
    - Jordan, Philip (Box A-68, Folder 75)
    - Jordan, George Reid (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-68, Folder 76)
    - Jordan, Richard (Box A-68, Folder 77)
    - Jordan, Richard Jr. (Box A-68, Folder 78)
    - Jordan, Robert (Box A-68, Folder 79)
    - Jordan, Ruel (Box A-68, Folder 80)
      Photographer if identified: M. Smith, Rapid News Photo
    - Jordan, Sara (Box A-68, Folder 81)
    - Jordan, Sarah (Box A-68, Folder 82)
    - Jordan, Stanley (Box A-68, Folder 83)
    - Jordan, Steve (Box A-68, Folder 84)
    - Jordan, Tenita (Box A-68, Folder 85)
    - Jordan, Thomas A. (Box A-68, Folder 86)
    - Jordan, Shirley (Box A-68, Folder 87)
    - Jordan, Tulani (Box A-68, Folder 88)
    - Jordan, Vernon (Mrs.) (Box A-68, Folder 89)
    - Jordan, Vernon E. (Box A-68, Folder 90)
      Also four velox prints. Two prints are stuck together with paste; one is mounted on cardstock.
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, Fabian Bachrach, Jerry Soalt, Whitestone Photo
    - Jordan, Vernon E. (Box A-68, Folder 91)
    - Jordan, Vernon E. (Box A-68, Folder 92)
      Photographer if identified: Billie Billing, Harris Photo, United Press International Photo
    - Jordan, Valerie (Box A-68, Folder 93)
      Also two velox prints. One print has single typescript leaf attached.
    - Jordan, Willis H. (Box A-68, Folder 94)
    - Jordan, Lonnie (Box A-68, Folder 95)
    - Jorge, Iva (Box A-68, Folder 96)
    - Jorsling, McDonald (Box A-68, Folder 97)
    - Joscelyn, Hamel C. (Box A-68, Folder 98)
    - Joseph, Alfred (Box A-68, Folder 99)
    - Joseph, Arnold (Dr.) (Box A-68, Folder 100)
      Photographer if identified: Hale Haberman
    - Joseph, Barbara (Box A-68, Folder 101)
    - Joseph, Cecil (Box A-68, Folder 102)
    - Joseph, Claire (Box A-68, Folder 103)
    - Joseph, Cliff (Box A-68, Folder 104)
    - Joseph, David (Box A-68, Folder 105)
    - Joseph, Dorothy D. (Box A-68, Folder 106)
    - Joseph, Ed (Box A-68, Folder 107)
    - Joseph, Eugene (Box A-68, Folder 108)
      Photographer if identified: Acton L. Lewis, National Assn. of Tax Accountants,
    - Joseph, Fritz E. (Box A-68, Folder 109)
    - Joseph, G.A. Jr. (Box A-68, Folder 110)
    - Joseph, Gene (Box A-68, Folder 111)
      Also one velox print/promotional card.
    - Joseph, Gloria (Dr.) (Box A-68, Folder 112)
    - Joseph, James (Box A-68, Folder 113)
    - Joseph, Jean (Box A-68, Folder 114)
    - Joseph, Keith Brian (Box A-68, Folder 115)
    - Joseph, Lavergue (Box A-68, Folder 116)
    - Joseph, Lawrence M. (Box A-68, Folder 117)
    - Joseph, Len (Box A-68, Folder 118)
      Also one velox print. One print has single manuscript leaf attached with staple on border; one print is cut out and mounted on paper.
    - Joseph, Lucille (Box A-68, Folder 119)
      Photo has been cut out.
    - Joseph, Lula (Mrs.) (Box A-68, Folder 120)
    - Joseph, Margie (Box A-68, Folder 121)
    - Joseph, Richard Anthony (Box A-68, Folder 122)
      Print is mounted on board along with a newspaper clipping.
    - Joseph, Selwyn (Box A-68, Folder 123)
    - Joseph, Tony (Box A-68, Folder 124)
      Photographer if identified: Alphonso Barrios
    - Jordan, Jack (Box A-68, Folder 125)
    - Josephs, Jennifer (Box A-68, Folder 126)
      Print has staple on border. Also one velox print.
    - Josephs, Margie (Box A-68, Folder 127)
    - Josephs, Peggy (Box A-68, Folder 128)
    - Josey, Kenneth (Box A-68, Folder 129)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, A. Hansen
    - Joshua, Charles (Box A-68, Folder 130)
    - Joshua, Chief (Box A-68, Folder 131)
    - Joshua, Harold (Box A-68, Folder 132)
    - Joshua, Helena (Box A-68, Folder 133)
    - Joshua, Sybyl (Box A-68, Folder 134)
    - Josie, Marva (Box A-68, Folder 135)
    - Jaubert, Doris (Box A-68, Folder 136)
    - Joubert, Joseph (Box A-68, Folder 137)
      Also one cut-out from a print publication.
    - Joubert, Phylis (Box A-68, Folder 138)
      Lengthy ms. caption written on verso.
    - Joubert, Samuel (Rev.) (Box A-68, Folder 139)
    - Joubert, Samuel (Dr.) (Box A-68, Folder 140)
    - Joudelson, David (Box A-68, Folder 141)
    - "Joulie African" (Box A-68, Folder 142)
    - Joy, Carol (Box A-68, Folder 143)
    - Joy, Crystal (Box A-68, Folder 144)
    - Joy, Daniel W. (Box A-68, Folder 145)
    - Joy, James (Box A-68, Folder 146)
    - "Joy Town" (Group) (Box A-68, Folder 147)
    - Joyce, Brenda (Box A-68, Folder 148)
      Incl. one envelope which reads "Emme Kemp" with two prints enclosed.
      Photographer if identified: Lois M. Weissflog
    - Joyce, Denice (Box A-68, Folder 149)
    - Joyce, Melba (Box A-68, Folder 150)
    - Joyettes, The (Box A-68, Folder 151)
    - Joyner, Aileen (Box A-68, Folder 152)
    - Joyner, Al (Box A-68, Folder 153)
      Photographer if identified: Tex Harris/Harris Photo
    - Joyner, Arthenia (Box A-68, Folder 154)
    - Joyner, Christopher (Box A-68, Folder 155)
      Print has single ms. leaf attached on verso with paperclip.
    - Joyner, Irving (Box A-68, Folder 156)
    - Joyner, Ivory Jr. (Box A-68, Folder 157)
      Also one manuscript leaf letter. One print is adhered to a piece of cardstock.
    - Joyner, Jackie (Box A-68, Folder 158)
    - Joyner, Sondra (Box A-68, Folder 159)
    - Joyner, J. (Box A-68, Folder 160)
    - Jubilation Quartet (Box A-68, Folder 161)
    - Jubilee, James (Box A-68, Folder 162)
    - Jubilee, Lenore (Box A-68, Folder 163)
    - Judah, Florine (Box A-68, Folder 164)
    - Judah, John P + L (Box A-68, Folder 165)
    - Judd, Barbara (Box A-68, Folder 166)
    - Judd, Bettye (Box A-68, Folder 167)
      Photographer if identified: Hayes/L.I.P.P.A.
    - Jude, Laura (Box A-68, Folder 168)
    - Jude, Odessa (Box A-68, Folder 169)
    - Judge, Beatrice M. (Box A-68, Folder 170)
      Note on folder: "Civil Court Judge."
    - Judkins, Flora (Box A-68, Folder 171)
    - Judo (Box A-68, Folder 172)
    - Judon, Dorothy (Box A-68, Folder 173)
    - Judon, Henri (Box A-68, Folder 174)
    - Judon, Henri (Mrs.) (Box A-68, Folder 175)
    - Judson, Horace (Dr.) (Box A-68, Folder 176)
    - Julia, Victor A. (Box A-68, Folder 177)
    - Julian, Percy Dr. (Box A-68, Folder 178)
    - Julien, Ernest (Box A-68, Folder 179)
    - Julien, Leo (Box A-68, Folder 180)
    - Julien, Wm. (Box A-68, Folder 181)
    - Julius, Reginald (Box A-68, Folder 182)
      Photographer if identified: Official F.D.N.Y. Photo by Fr. F. Murphy
    - Julius, Vincent + Reginald (Box A-68, Folder 183)
    - Julliard, Argus Speare (Box A-68, Folder 184)
    - Juilliard School (Box A-68, Folder 185)
    - Julliard String Quartet (Box A-68, Folder 186)
      Photographer if identified: Alix B. Williamson
    - Jumel, Mansion (Box A-68, Folder 187)
    - Jumelle, Gaston Dr. (Box A-68, Folder 188)
    - June, Louis R. (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-68, Folder 189)
    - June, Mae (Box A-68, Folder 190)
    - Jungle Allies (Box A-68, Folder 191)
      Note on folder: "by A.C. Hollingsworth."
    - Junie (Box A-68, Folder 192)
    - Junior (Box A-68, Folder 193)
    - Junior, Ollie (Box A-68, Folder 194)
    - Jurgensen, Rudolph (Box A-68, Folder 195)
    - Justice (Mr.) (Box A-68, Folder 196)
    - Justice, Barbar (Dr.) (Box A-68, Folder 197)
    - Justice, Walter (Box A-68, Folder 198)
    - Julien, Alice (Mrs.) (Box A-68, Folder 199)
    - Julian, Hubert F. (Box A-68, Folder 200)
      Also two velox prints adhered on opposites sides of a piece of paper and an additional velox print.
    - Julian, Max (Box A-68, Folder 201)
    - Junor, John (Box OS-1, Folder 2)
    - "Just Us" (Box A-68, Folder 202)
    - Justice, Jeff (Box A-68, Folder 203)